[Script Info]
; This is an Advanced Sub Station Alpha v4+ script.
; For Sub Station Alpha info and downloads,
; go to http://www.eswat.demon.co.uk/
; or email kotus@eswat.demon.co.uk
; 
; Advanced Sub Station Alpha script format developed by #Anime-Fansubs@EfNET
; http://www.anime-fansubs.org
; 
; For additional info and downloads go to http://vobsub.edensrising.com/
; or email gabest@freemail.hu
; 
; Note: This file was saved by Subresync.
; 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 704
PlayResY: 480
Timer: 100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: None,Benguiat Medium,14,&H00f4f4fd,&H000000ff,&H00000000,&H80000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,2,0,0,0,1
Style: Overlap,Benguiat Medium,30,&H00fffbf3,&H000000ff,&H00000000,&H80000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,2,60,60,26,1
Style: Default,楷体,28,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00040409,&HF0FCFCFC,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: warning,方正准圆_GBK,25,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,2,8,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.37,0:00:07.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本作品由----C.mp个人制作 仅供学习交流试看之用 请在12小时内删除并支持正版 严禁作为商业用途 本人不承担任何法律责任.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.37,0:00:23.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.46,0:00:32.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天....天使！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.63,0:01:03.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,汉化 校对 润色 封装 字幕作者：----蔡孟浦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.20,0:01:13.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天使！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.76,0:01:17.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是天使么？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.40,0:01:21.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.34,0:01:25.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吾辈是死之天使在地上的代行人
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.68,0:01:29.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在既是审判之时 以神的名义····
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.56,0:01:43.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被告：不列颠
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.97,0:01:46.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被告：怪物
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.57,0:01:48.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,判决：死刑
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.21,0:01:49.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死刑！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.59,0:01:51.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死刑！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.83,0:01:53.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死刑！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.63,0:01:59.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为此我非常遗憾 亲爱的罪人们
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.35,0:02:02.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然而 （罪）总不得赦免！（注：出自《圣经》）
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.38,0:02:06.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像凋谢的花一般死去吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.38,0:02:06.25,warning,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,引用：凡有血气的尽皆如草 花必凋谢 草必枯干\N《圣经 旧约 赛40:6-8；新约 彼得前1:24-25》
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.25,0:02:10.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,微不足道的生命 背负这沉重的扼死去吧！\N（像蝴蝶一般飞舞 像蜜蜂一样死去）
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.10,0:02:28.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好 很好...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.66,0:02:30.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个男孩...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.08,0:02:32.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从未将他视为熟睡的狮子（表示欣赏）
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.78,0:02:33.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少....少校
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.94,0:02:35.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少校！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.02,0:02:36.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里很危险！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.40,0:02:38.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请回到飞艇里面！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.31,0:02:43.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,博士, 那东西准备好了么？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.06,0:02:45.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是....是的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.10,0:02:54.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然危险 但按照您的指示进行了手术 现在还不是太稳定
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.45,0:02:57.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常好
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.01,0:02:58.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他很完美不是么？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.92,0:03:03.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的确是完美的素体
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.55,0:03:06.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干得不错, 博士
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.31,0:03:09.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也给我稍微做点正事 笨蛋！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.30,0:03:10.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才没有偷懒！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.68,0:03:13.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要忘了 我可是跑去HellSing 去看了索林(Zorin)
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.62,0:03:14.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 好像是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.00,0:03:22.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Achtung(注意)！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.72,0:03:27.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大队全员装备反紫外线装备
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.89,0:03:29.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,集合！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.06,0:03:33.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,装备面罩！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.52,0:03:39.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全体集合 全体集合！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.47,0:04:07.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,据守此地！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.02,0:04:09.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,攻占他土！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.84,0:04:13.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,眼之所见即为坟茔 将神（我们）的仇敌彻底埋葬！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.06,0:04:15.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,目标：前方
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.77,0:04:18.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,执行死刑
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.86,0:04:52.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少校, 请快回到里面
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.57,0:04:56.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这艘飞艇虽是用特殊的轻金属装甲，但也支撑不了多久
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.70,0:04:58.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少校....
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.21,0:05:08.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他在指挥...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.78,0:05:10.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,战争的乐章！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.94,0:05:34.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有人能打扰他的演奏
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.23,0:05:37.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们都是他指挥下的乐器
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.62,0:05:42.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咆哮着 嘶吼着 在这战场上一只演奏的工具
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.96,0:05:45.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无人能使他停下
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.75,0:05:55.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确认 敌方统帅！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.28,0:05:56.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他在飞艇上方！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.12,0:05:58.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他到底在做什么?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.97,0:06:02.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死的魔鬼 和你的战场一起下地狱歌唱吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.37,0:06:10.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少校！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.52,0:06:11.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.56,0:06:27.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干得好 管家.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.40,0:06:48.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,半个世纪前就已经决定好了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.41,0:06:51.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骷髅的印记最适合死神！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.59,0:07:12.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是来就我们的么?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.15,0:07:20.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死！死！死！死！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.95,0:07:23.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这样 将他们全都杀了！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.92,0:07:25.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卑微的虫子
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.56,0:07:28.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,趁着活着的时候!看着我们
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.13,0:07:30.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看啊 这就是Vatican（梵蒂冈）的权柄！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.88,0:07:34.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有死的新教徒才是好的新教徒！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.38,0:07:47.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你背叛了我们, Maxwell (马克斯维尔)
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.89,0:07:52.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,战争中 欺骗和背叛是理所当然的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.49,0:07:56.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相反 他们应该得到称赞
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.75,0:07:59.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尤其是在对付异教徒是时候
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.00,0:08:03.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是....
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.72,0:08:07.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是 这完全不同
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.74,0:08:10.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我厌恶如此！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.54,0:08:14.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马克斯维尔 你醉了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.82,0:08:19.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全沉醉在欲望和权力之中
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.45,0:08:25.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吾辈犹大（背叛者）本应作为暴力的工具
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.90,0:08:28.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是一把消除罪人的刀
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.46,0:08:31.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吾辈只是神在地上执行岔怒的仆人
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.31,0:08:37.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马克斯维尔 你放弃了侍奉吾主！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.20,0:08:39.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唯独侍奉吾主的力量！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.08,0:08:45.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 马克斯维尔大主教？！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.03,0:08:47.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安德森神父
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.80,0:08:51.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们刚收到马克斯维尔大主教的命令
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.31,0:08:55.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即刻拘束并押送HellSing的局长因特古拉
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.52,0:09:01.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我非常不爽
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.79,0:09:06.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这并不是您个人心情的问题 安德森！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.93,0:09:09.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我十分不爽!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.74,0:09:20.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塞拉斯
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.58,0:09:22.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塞拉斯.维克多利亚
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.44,0:09:25.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事吧 因特古拉局长？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.94,0:09:27.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还活着
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.72,0:09:29.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总部如何?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.81,0:09:34.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,受到了大规模的攻击 敌人已经全歼
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.25,0:09:39.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但总部也被彻底破坏
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.19,0:09:43.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贝尔纳特队长也....
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.76,0:09:48.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是么 原来如此
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.70,0:09:52.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塞拉斯 , 贝尔纳特的生命流淌在你的体内（你喝了贝尔纳特的血）？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.48,0:09:56.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你成为真正的吸血鬼了吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.36,0:10:00.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是....是的！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.56,0:10:02.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.55,0:10:08.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们是无法击败这个女孩的.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.56,0:10:12.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,The vampire（吸血鬼）, 塞拉斯.维克多利亚
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.92,0:10:18.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经变成了令人畏惧的怪物了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.23,0:10:22.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 神父亚历山大.安德森
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.23,0:10:25.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经无所畏惧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.59,0:10:29.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的眼神像是从地狱里爬出的魔鬼一般
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.72,0:10:33.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拥有人的模样 和与之相反的事实（怪物）
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.25,0:10:42.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个人....
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.38,0:10:45.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.93,0:10:53.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可精彩了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.87,0:10:55.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有的计划都泡汤了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.02,0:11:03.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Thames（泰晤士河）有不明物体逆流而上
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.81,0:11:05.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.83,0:11:11.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幽灵....船？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.97,0:13:11.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曾经在枪林（油画）前齐聚的我们
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.50,0:13:16.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,此刻又如此一样在枪林前再会
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.20,0:13:24.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,德意志第三帝国,吸血鬼花装甲掷弹兵战斗集团
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.95,0:13:28.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,残存兵力 572
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.18,0:13:35.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罗马天主教梵蒂冈教皇厅 第九次空中机动十字军
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.93,0:13:40.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,残存兵力 2875
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.21,0:13:45.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大英帝国 皇立国教骑士团
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.76,0:13:50.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,残存兵力 3
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.19,0:13:56.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在(这样)，演员们全部出场了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.17,0:13:59.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在是时候揭开序幕:黎明前的魔女之夜(Walpurgis)
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.17,0:13:59.89,warning,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Walpurgis即瓦尔普吉斯之夜 《浮士德》有描述 为督伊德教的一个节日
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.49,0:14:14.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主人!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.97,0:14:18.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的主人 因特古拉·海辛！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.23,0:14:19.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我命令！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.00,0:14:25.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的仆人 吸血鬼阿卡多
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.39,0:14:30.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以白银之枪将白衣军团染至深红！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.24,0:14:36.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以黑铁之铳将黑衣军团染至深红！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.68,0:14:43.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将敌人的一切尽皆染至深红！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.51,0:14:45.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,见敌必杀！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.05,0:14:46.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,见敌必杀！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.87,0:14:50.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将敌人尽数屠杀！无人可活着离开这个岛国！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.87,0:14:54.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,任务确认
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.40,0:14:58.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如您所愿 我的主人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.04,0:15:06.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,限制禁缚术0式 解放
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.83,0:15:08.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,归来吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.36,0:15:11.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千万之众归来吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.77,0:15:12.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咏唱
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.31,0:15:21.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,The Bird of the Hermes is my name.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.31,0:15:21.86,warning,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（出自炼金术文献《The Ripley Scroll》）
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.65,0:15:45.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,I devoured my own wings！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.27,0:16:12.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里的每个人都感到了恐惧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.72,0:16:17.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果不将这个怪物消灭，就会发生可怕的事
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.56,0:16:23.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,That's how I was tamed
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.22,0:16:34.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要来了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.13,0:16:39.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,河流要来了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.00,0:16:41.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死之河
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.16,0:16:44.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死者舞蹈
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.45,0:16:48.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,地狱也为之歌唱
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.40,0:18:07.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么.... 可能
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.92,0:18:09.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不可能!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.50,0:18:11.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会有这样的事！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.51,0:18:15.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是吸血鬼 阿卡多
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.89,0:18:21.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,血：是灵魂的通货 生命的货币
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.52,0:18:24.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,饮食他血 这就是生命交易的方式
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.87,0:18:29.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,意味着将他人的生命占为己有
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.24,0:18:34.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在的你应该能理解了吧 塞拉斯.维克多利亚
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.68,0:18:39.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.73,0:18:45.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,战锅旗....
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.18,0:18:47.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Janissaries军团！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.66,0:18:50.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你连他们都吃掉了么！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.16,0:18:53.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难怪你死不掉
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.37,0:18:55.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也杀不掉
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.05,0:18:59.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你究竟拥有多少生命？！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.30,0:19:02.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有多少生命因此消耗殆尽？！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.10,0:19:11.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Wallachia....
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.71,0:19:13.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,皇家骑士团....
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.35,0:19:19.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你....
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.56,0:19:20.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你连自己的军队....
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.86,0:19:22.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自己的仆人....
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.22,0:19:24.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自己的平民也....
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.86,0:19:27.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你究竟是什么, 怪物？！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.50,0:19:29.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,魔鬼！魔鬼！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.42,0:19:30.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,魔鬼！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.79,0:20:18.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全面防御！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.63,0:20:21.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,撤退！防御！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.50,0:20:22.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了？！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.68,0:20:24.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底发生了什么？！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.54,0:20:26.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死亡
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.62,0:20:30.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死亡降临了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.08,0:20:39.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多惊人啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.99,0:20:41.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这才是我们想要的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.04,0:20:42.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太棒了！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.99,0:20:46.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,射击
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.14,0:20:47.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将他们击杀
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.52,0:20:49.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,集中火力
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.06,0:21:16.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,射击！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.86,0:21:18.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,射击！射击！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.12,0:21:20.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,战场下面是地狱 地狱
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.78,0:21:23.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论怎么射击 还是不断的涌出来
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.10,0:21:45.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一防线已被彻底摧毁
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.43,0:21:48.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主教 我们必须撤退！主教！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.55,0:21:50.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这已经不是战争了 这是屠杀！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.54,0:21:53.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开什么玩笑 主教？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.13,0:21:56.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是大主教
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.76,0:21:58.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大主教！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.05,0:22:28.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可是用似曜岩复合强化的玻璃
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.96,0:22:31.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们是不无法破坏其分毫的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.46,0:22:38.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安　安德森
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.57,0:22:45.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安德森
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.22,0:22:55.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吾辈是Iscariot（加略人 犹大的姓即叛徒）, 吾是神罚在地上的代行人
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.95,0:23:01.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吾将粉碎你那可伶的梦想 没有一丝怜悯（遗憾）
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.47,0:23:05.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见了  吾友
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.11,0:23:14.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安德森！安德森！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.49,0:23:16.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安德森！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.69,0:23:21.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,救我 安德森！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:21.87,0:23:23.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,救我 神父！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.80,0:23:25.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神父（老师）
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.23,0:23:28.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神父（老师）....
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.35,0:23:38.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我为什么会在这里？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.73,0:23:41.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道我要如此孤独的死去？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.75,0:23:42.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.54,0:23:45.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.08,0:23:50.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,孤独的活着 孤独的死去?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:55.69,0:23:57.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Jesus（耶稣）...
Dialogue: 0,0:24:12.51,0:24:13.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师
Dialogue: 0,0:24:14.37,0:24:16.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安德森老师
Dialogue: 0,0:24:19.79,0:24:21.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要成为伟大的人
Dialogue: 0,0:24:21.81,0:24:23.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我.....
Dialogue: 0,0:24:23.28,0:24:27.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要站在最顶端 俯视每一个人
Dialogue: 0,0:24:33.10,0:24:35.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是一个傻瓜
Dialogue: 0,0:24:39.86,0:24:42.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无可救药的傻瓜
Dialogue: 0,0:24:49.39,0:24:53.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是安德森 所有武装神父（分部）
Dialogue: 0,0:24:53.39,0:24:55.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即刻撤回Vatican（梵蒂冈）
Dialogue: 0,0:24:57.97,0:25:03.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第九次远征十字军 全军覆没
Dialogue: 0,0:25:06.58,0:25:08.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拂晓将至
Dialogue: 0,0:25:08.01,0:25:10.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梦醒此时
Dialogue: 0,0:25:11.34,0:25:13.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回梵蒂冈去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:25:13.23,0:25:15.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但....但是 安德森！
Dialogue: 0,0:25:16.09,0:25:19.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里并不是你们休息的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:25:19.41,0:25:20.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都回去！
Dialogue: 0,0:25:20.86,0:25:22.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,守护梵蒂冈
Dialogue: 0,0:25:23.76,0:25:25.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,守护教皇
Dialogue: 0,0:25:25.96,0:25:29.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,永远守护天主教
Dialogue: 0,0:25:31.26,0:25:34.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要打倒他
Dialogue: 0,0:25:34.90,0:25:37.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打倒那名为阿卡多的男人！
Dialogue: 0,0:25:37.40,0:25:38.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无后路可退！
Dialogue: 0,0:25:39.21,0:25:40.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神父先生
Dialogue: 0,0:25:40.25,0:25:43.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,与之争斗 尔之何如？（和他战斗 您会怎样）
Dialogue: 0,0:25:43.09,0:25:44.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无所谓
Dialogue: 0,0:25:44.18,0:25:46.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有此刻
Dialogue: 0,0:25:46.54,0:25:49.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿卡多所有的禁制完全解放的现在
Dialogue: 0,0:25:49.91,0:25:52.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,预计好的时刻正向我们走来
Dialogue: 0,0:25:52.90,0:25:59.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是他将拥有的生命完全释放并令其全部攻击的禁制
Dialogue: 0,0:26:00.14,0:26:04.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像一座城池所有的士兵全数出击
Dialogue: 0,0:26:04.78,0:26:07.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,领主立于城中....
Dialogue: 0,0:26:07.63,0:26:09.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有一人！
Dialogue: 0,0:26:10.36,0:26:13.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有现在 他才是单独的吸血鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:26:13.45,0:26:15.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唯一的伯爵（Dracula即德古拉）
Dialogue: 0,0:26:16.77,0:26:23.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐怕这才是那疯子（少校）的真正目的
Dialogue: 0,0:26:23.13,0:26:28.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有的一切其实只是为了打倒阿卡多的献祭
Dialogue: 0,0:26:29.52,0:26:33.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上千人的武装纳粹党卫军，三千人的十字军
Dialogue: 0,0:26:33.02,0:26:37.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,数百万计的英国人
Dialogue: 0,0:26:38.41,0:26:42.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就连我也被算计在内
Dialogue: 0,0:26:43.62,0:26:45.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见了 我的朋友们
Dialogue: 0,0:26:45.27,0:26:47.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马克斯维尔在哭泣！
Dialogue: 0,0:26:48.44,0:26:52.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个无可救药的傻瓜！
Dialogue: 0,0:26:53.23,0:26:57.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使在死亡到来之时 依旧孤独一人！
Dialogue: 0,0:26:58.15,0:26:59.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别了
Dialogue: 0,0:26:59.85,0:27:01.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,地狱的边境(Limbo)我们再会
Dialogue: 0,0:27:01.79,0:27:02.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神父先生!
Dialogue: 0,0:27:02.58,0:27:04.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安德森神父！
Dialogue: 0,0:27:44.47,0:27:47.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎回来 伯爵
Dialogue: 0,0:27:52.53,0:27:54.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了,（女）伯爵
Dialogue: 0,0:27:58.99,0:28:02.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢....欢迎回来 主人
Dialogue: 0,0:28:08.67,0:28:11.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主....主人 原来有胡子呢?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:13.57,0:28:14.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胡子....
Dialogue: 0,0:28:28.85,0:28:30.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塞拉斯
Dialogue: 0,0:28:32.59,0:28:34.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塞拉斯.维克多利亚
Dialogue: 0,0:29:01.86,0:29:04.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,漂亮 我的宿敌
Dialogue: 0,0:29:05.24,0:29:07.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吾辈是神的仆人
Dialogue: 0,0:29:07.86,0:29:10.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是神罚在地上的代行者
Dialogue: 0,0:29:10.70,0:29:14.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吾辈的使命是将渎神的愚者....
Dialogue: 0,0:29:14.33,0:29:18.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最后一丝血肉也灭绝殆尽！
Dialogue: 0,0:29:26.58,0:29:32.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿门！
Dialogue: 0,0:29:52.91,0:29:56.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,血肉之躯居然能锻炼如斯境界
Dialogue: 0,0:29:59.96,0:30:02.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的仇敌, 来杀我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:30:02.96,0:30:06.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将铳剑刺入我的心脏
Dialogue: 0,0:30:06.85,0:30:11.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像五百年前和一百年前那样....
Dialogue: 0,0:30:11.39,0:30:15.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结束我那遥不可及的梦
Dialogue: 0,0:30:15.42,0:30:17.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我亲爱的宿敌啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:30:18.89,0:30:20.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不用你说
Dialogue: 0,0:30:41.82,0:30:46.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Macedonian公司特制的纯银弹壳 经过洗礼的水银弹头
Dialogue: 0,0:30:46.33,0:30:49.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Marvell's公司特制火药：NNA9
Dialogue: 0,0:30:49.58,0:30:56.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,39cm 16kg 13mm爆裂穿甲弹
Dialogue: 0,0:30:56.07,0:30:57.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,The Jackal！
Dialogue: 0,0:30:57.71,0:30:59.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完美啊 Walter（管家的名字）！
Dialogue: 0,0:31:35.36,0:31:36.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办？
Dialogue: 0,0:31:37.01,0:31:38.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要怎么办？
Dialogue: 0,0:31:38.63,0:31:42.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怪物就站在你面前 天主教徒（Catholic）
Dialogue: 0,0:31:42.96,0:31:44.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要怎么战胜我呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:31:44.93,0:31:47.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有多少胜算呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:31:47.19,0:31:48.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千分之一....
Dialogue: 0,0:31:48.76,0:31:50.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,万分之一....
Dialogue: 0,0:31:50.41,0:31:52.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,百万分之一 十亿分之一....
Dialogue: 0,0:31:52.09,0:31:54.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是万亿分之一？
Dialogue: 0,0:31:54.64,0:32:00.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使是无限的尽头 对我而言也足够了！
Dialogue: 0,0:32:01.65,0:32:04.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,与Nordland小队失去联系
Dialogue: 0,0:32:01.65,0:32:04.03,warning,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Nordland：纳粹党第11装甲掷弹兵师团的代号

Dialogue: 0,0:32:04.03,0:32:05.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回击, 蠢货！
Dialogue: 0,0:32:05.77,0:32:07.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,空中巡航舰发来电报：
Dialogue: 0,0:32:07.29,0:32:10.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Burgerbraukeller小队的火力消耗殆尽）
Dialogue: 0,0:32:07.29,0:32:10.53,warning,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Burgerbraukeller：德国二战时期著名酒馆

Dialogue: 0,0:32:10.53,0:32:11.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无人回应！
Dialogue: 0,0:32:12.25,0:32:16.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,管家, 给我一杯Van Houten牌的cocoa饮料
Dialogue: 0,0:32:16.77,0:32:19.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,牛奶和糖都要
Dialogue: 0,0:32:22.82,0:32:25.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伦敦陷落了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:25.12,0:32:27.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,十字军也溃败了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:27.38,0:32:30.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连Last Battalion（最后的大队）也逐渐毁灭
Dialogue: 0,0:32:31.24,0:32:34.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仅剩下阿卡多...
Dialogue: 0,0:32:35.17,0:32:38.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有我在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:32:39.38,0:32:42.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很完美
Dialogue: 0,0:32:42.17,0:32:45.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,计划进行非常顺利
Dialogue: 0,0:32:56.97,0:32:59.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了？ 基督徒
Dialogue: 0,0:32:59.23,0:33:01.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怪物就在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:33:06.10,0:33:08.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,满身疮痍的你能做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:33:08.51,0:33:11.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的胳膊都要掉下来了
Dialogue: 0,0:33:11.43,0:33:13.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你该如何是好呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:33:14.15,0:33:16.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是狗？
Dialogue: 0,0:33:16.25,0:33:18.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是人？
Dialogue: 0,0:33:20.28,0:33:23.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那又如何,吸血鬼？
Dialogue: 0,0:33:24.72,0:33:28.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只不过是胳膊断了而已
Dialogue: 0,0:33:28.55,0:33:31.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要虚张声势
Dialogue: 0,0:33:31.02,0:33:31.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,攻过来吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:33:31.78,0:33:34.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Hurry！ Hurry！
Dialogue: 0,0:33:41.66,0:33:43.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多令人吃惊啊
Dialogue: 0,0:33:47.97,0:33:51.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人类果然是最值得钦佩的
Dialogue: 0,0:34:25.15,0:34:26.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,炸裂链
Dialogue: 0,0:34:37.67,0:34:38.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,向前！
Dialogue: 0,0:34:40.26,0:34:41.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,向前！
Dialogue: 0,0:34:41.60,0:34:43.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,向前！向前！向前！
Dialogue: 0,0:34:43.87,0:34:45.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,向前！向前！
Dialogue: 0,0:34:46.84,0:34:48.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多么了不起的男人....
Dialogue: 0,0:34:50.88,0:34:52.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,简直...
Dialogue: 0,0:34:52.31,0:34:54.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,简直就像那些男人一样
Dialogue: 0,0:34:56.28,0:34:57.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:34:57.44,0:35:01.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快来吧 亚历山大.安德森！
Dialogue: 0,0:35:01.71,0:35:04.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,站在我的面前
Dialogue: 0,0:35:04.81,0:35:06.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像那些男人一样....
Dialogue: 0,0:35:06.75,0:35:08.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像那个男人一样！
Dialogue: 0,0:35:08.93,0:35:14.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想看见你站在那儿 刺穿我的心脏
Dialogue: 0,0:35:17.53,0:35:20.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,滚开！
Dialogue: 0,0:35:41.21,0:35:43.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们这群白痴！
Dialogue: 0,0:35:44.38,0:35:46.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们这群愚蠢的白痴！
Dialogue: 0,0:35:47.83,0:35:50.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果就这样回梵蒂冈！
Dialogue: 0,0:35:50.02,0:35:52.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么我们与信仰即背道而驰 我们不再是我们！
Dialogue: 0,0:35:52.99,0:35:55.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不再是背叛者13科
Dialogue: 0,0:35:55.79,0:35:59.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仅仅只是一推行尸走肉罢了
Dialogue: 0,0:35:59.51,0:36:05.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们早已有方向：就是清除所有的异教徒和怪物\N（吾辈是神在地上的唯一代行人）
Dialogue: 0,0:36:05.49,0:36:08.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些不就是您教导我们的么？
Dialogue: 0,0:36:08.49,0:36:12.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在我们来证明这一切并不只是一个狂热的幻想！
Dialogue: 0,0:36:12.79,0:36:14.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们这群傻瓜！
Dialogue: 0,0:36:14.81,0:36:18.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果每一个人都一心求死
Dialogue: 0,0:36:18.29,0:36:20.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,地狱的边境可无法承载我们的灵魂！
Dialogue: 0,0:36:21.20,0:36:23.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那好吧 随我来
Dialogue: 0,0:36:23.37,0:36:26.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,向着地狱前进吧
Dialogue: 0,0:36:27.36,0:36:29.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如曾经一样 我们一同赴死！
Dialogue: 0,0:36:29.80,0:36:31.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尔等为何？！
Dialogue: 0,0:36:31.95,0:36:35.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是背叛者 背叛者犹大
Dialogue: 0,0:36:40.26,0:36:43.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有的生命有着同一个渴望
Dialogue: 0,0:36:43.90,0:36:49.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像幼虫一样蠕动 像花草一般枯萎\N（无数生命蠕动 挣扎 如同一个生命）
Dialogue: 0,0:36:49.93,0:36:53.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,流着血 并渴望（血）
Dialogue: 0,0:36:53.00,0:36:59.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如此的轮回着 战斗着
Dialogue: 0,0:36:59.53,0:37:03.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对于天主教徒来说 这是他们的“神”（信仰）
Dialogue: 0,0:37:03.48,0:37:06.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对于纳粹党人来说 是获得战争的胜利
Dialogue: 0,0:37:06.43,0:37:10.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对于阿卡多....
Dialogue: 0,0:37:10.38,0:37:14.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仔细一想 我们拥有同样的目的
Dialogue: 0,0:37:14.60,0:37:16.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,复兴同一个梦想
Dialogue: 0,0:37:17.85,0:37:20.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见了 我黑色的兄弟们
Dialogue: 0,0:37:22.26,0:37:23.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先走一步
Dialogue: 0,0:37:23.02,0:37:23.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:37:25.68,0:37:27.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿门！
Dialogue: 0,0:37:28.86,0:37:30.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我走了
Dialogue: 0,0:38:03.60,0:38:06.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你终于站在我面前了么？
Dialogue: 0,0:38:07.91,0:38:09.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做的好....
Dialogue: 0,0:38:09.99,0:38:12.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不愧是Iscariot（背叛者犹大）
Dialogue: 0,0:38:12.81,0:38:15.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不愧是亚历山大.安德森！
Dialogue: 0,0:38:22.87,0:38:28.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拥有武器的并不只有你一个
Dialogue: 0,0:38:28.69,0:38:32.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是你们的王牌么?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:46.61,0:38:47.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是钉子么？
Dialogue: 0,0:38:47.97,0:38:50.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,裹尸布....
Dialogue: 0,0:38:50.01,0:38:51.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圣杯....
Dialogue: 0,0:38:51.56,0:38:53.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朗基努斯之枪....
Dialogue: 0,0:38:53.43,0:38:58.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从罗马消失的最后一件圣遗物
Dialogue: 0,0:38:58.83,0:39:00.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:00.56,0:39:02.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奇迹的遗香....（The lingering scent of a miracle）
Dialogue: 0,0:39:02.82,0:39:04.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海琳娜的圣钉（Helena's nail）
Dialogue: 0,0:39:05.52,0:39:07.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是她
Dialogue: 0,0:39:07.21,0:39:09.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手 安德森
Dialogue: 0,0:39:09.90,0:39:12.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要抛弃自己的灵魂成为怪物么？
Dialogue: 0,0:39:12.16,0:39:14.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成为神的怪物么？
Dialogue: 0,0:39:14.49,0:39:18.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一具拥有神的力量的永恒容器么？
Dialogue: 0,0:39:18.58,0:39:19.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也一样么
Dialogue: 0,0:39:19.96,0:39:22.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像他们一样的狗屎
Dialogue: 0,0:39:22.32,0:39:26.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,认同神与否定神的怪物么？
Dialogue: 0,0:39:27.95,0:39:30.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,使用那种奇迹的残骸 意味着....
Dialogue: 0,0:39:30.79,0:39:33.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也打算成为奇迹的残骸么?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:34.59,0:39:38.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你和我....
Dialogue: 0,0:39:38.10,0:39:43.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的战斗 驱使着我们走向地狱的尽头
Dialogue: 0,0:39:45.29,0:39:47.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像我这样....
Dialogue: 0,0:39:47.93,0:39:52.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抛弃人类身份的弱小怪物
Dialogue: 0,0:39:52.39,0:39:56.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会试图毁灭自己的一切！
Dialogue: 0,0:40:06.02,0:40:08.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手 人类
Dialogue: 0,0:40:08.66,0:40:13.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要成为像我一样的怪物
Dialogue: 0,0:40:16.93,0:40:19.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我仅仅是一把铳剑
Dialogue: 0,0:40:20.40,0:40:23.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一把承载神罚的铳剑而已
Dialogue: 0,0:40:24.84,0:40:28.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吾愿生来即是风暴
Dialogue: 0,0:40:28.64,0:40:31.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吾愿生来即是危险
Dialogue: 0,0:40:31.24,0:40:34.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吾愿生来即是毁灭
Dialogue: 0,0:40:34.25,0:40:39.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吾愿生来即无血无泪 只是无情的飓风
Dialogue: 0,0:40:40.37,0:40:44.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果她能使之如愿....
Dialogue: 0,0:40:45.93,0:40:48.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就这样吧
Dialogue: 0,0:41:22.54,0:41:25.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你....你这....
Dialogue: 0,0:41:41.10,0:41:43.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无可救药的蠢材!
Dialogue: 0,0:42:17.51,0:42:19.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,荆棘....
Dialogue: 0,0:42:19.19,0:42:20.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,荆棘....
Dialogue: 0,0:42:20.29,0:42:21.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安德森...
Dialogue: 0,0:42:21.64,0:42:24.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你究竟成为了什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:42:24.82,0:42:28.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他已经不再是人类
Dialogue: 0,0:42:28.89,0:42:34.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有凿毁这里 才能与世长辞
Dialogue: 0,0:42:36.28,0:42:39.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心脏
Dialogue: 0,0:42:40.37,0:42:41.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安德森神父
Dialogue: 0,0:42:41.83,0:42:42.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神父先生
Dialogue: 0,0:43:44.41,0:43:48.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他不是人类 亦不是魔鬼....
Dialogue: 0,0:43:48.85,0:43:52.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不属于白昼 也不属于黑夜....
Dialogue: 0,0:44:55.81,0:44:57.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Master(主人)！
