[Script Info]
; This is an Advanced Sub Station Alpha v4+ script.
; For Sub Station Alpha info and downloads,
; go to http://www.eswat.demon.co.uk/
; or email kotus@eswat.demon.co.uk
; 
; Advanced Sub Station Alpha script format developed by #Anime-Fansubs@EfNET
; http://www.anime-fansubs.org
; 
; For additional info and downloads go to http://vobsub.edensrising.com/
; or email gabest@freemail.hu
; 
; Note: This file was saved by Subresync.
; 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 704
PlayResY: 480
Timer: 100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,楷体,28,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00040409,&HF0FCFCFC,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.73,0:00:18.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,做得还真是过分呢
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.18,0:00:22.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的主人 我的仆人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.72,0:00:26.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样下去大家都要破产了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.60,0:00:27.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么接下来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.49,0:00:29.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,让我拭目以待吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.56,0:00:37.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,无聊的开场该结束了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.90,0:00:41.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Hellsing的高潮到来了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.28,0:01:14.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.16,0:01:17.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你和我的死吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.24,0:01:19.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们的死吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.75,0:01:31.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,全部都笑着死去了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.80,0:01:36.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 他们到这里来就是赴死的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.78,0:01:39.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就这么想死么
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.67,0:01:41.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真就这么想死吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.74,0:01:42.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,随便去死好了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.45,0:01:45.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,50年前就该去死了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.72,0:01:51.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样讲可不行哦 小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.08,0:01:55.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,单纯去死是绝对不行的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.40,0:02:00.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们都是不可救药的人
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.20,0:02:05.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,全世界的人都认为我们没有存在的必要
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.69,0:02:12.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,全世界的人都打算把我们忘得一干二净
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.39,0:02:17.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是要知道我们的存在对我们来说是必需的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.36,0:02:20.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,毫无理由的去死 我们最讨厌了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.21,0:02:22.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个最讨厌
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.52,0:02:26.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们有比死亡更重要的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.15,0:02:29.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,更重要 更更重要
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.38,0:02:32.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这就是我们来此的原因
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.07,0:02:34.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,将死亡延后
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.62,0:02:38.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,会有更多
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.73,0:02:40.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一定还会有很多
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.73,0:02:42.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一定有会某个战斗的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.25,0:02:45.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一定有会某个战斗的敌人
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.52,0:02:48.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,世界大得很
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.77,0:02:51.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,充斥着威胁与奇观
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.47,0:02:54.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,战争和炮灰满眼都是
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.57,0:03:04.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个世上一定存在的比起死亡更需要的多的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.90,0:03:07.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们到死是为了追求的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.10,0:03:10.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,更需要东西
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.56,0:03:16.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不然我们就无法朝着无限的领域走的更远
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.32,0:03:19.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以我们不能死
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.61,0:03:21.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以你们很可怜
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.02,0:03:24.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们只有那个价值
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.83,0:03:27.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们很棒
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.29,0:03:31.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,王立国教骑士团 Hellsing
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.39,0:03:36.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们对我们来说是有死亡的价值的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.49,0:03:40.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们对我们来说是为了被我们杀死而存在的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.90,0:03:44.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因特古拉大人 请你先走
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.96,0:03:46.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,塞拉斯
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.38,0:03:48.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快点 到那个少校那里去
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.14,0:03:49.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个男人
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.34,0:03:51.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,已经不能再让那个男人
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.45,0:03:54.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再多少一句话了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.69,0:04:00.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要死掉
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.82,0:04:03.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不允许哦 塞拉斯
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.26,0:04:06.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,绝对不允许
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.91,0:04:17.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是只忠诚的狗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.91,0:04:29.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,辛苦了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.08,0:05:57.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是场恶劣的赌局啊 沃尔特
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.39,0:06:01.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不久后 你的牌也会坠落燃烧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.86,0:06:05.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你的主人被我的主人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.18,0:06:08.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你的后辈被我的后辈
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.57,0:06:13.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而你也要被我杀掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.84,0:06:16.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,残酷的末路啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.91,0:06:21.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我可没有兴趣陪你玩你赌上人生的赌局
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.47,0:06:25.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而你 只是一个叛徒
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.58,0:06:26.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,叛徒而已
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.81,0:06:32.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,从我出生到现在从来没有原谅过一个背叛者
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.63,0:06:35.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不管什么时候 我都对有那种行为的人...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.24,0:06:38.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有一对一战斗的冲动
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.97,0:06:41.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不过 你还是快点去死吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.37,0:06:44.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为 我肚子饿了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.64,0:07:26.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就连我都不知道能不能把这个吃完
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.66,0:07:34.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,全都变成你期待的那样了 少校
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.33,0:07:39.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对啊 全都是我想的那样
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.83,0:07:42.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他又开始构筑城墙了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.47,0:07:45.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我赢了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.69,0:07:50.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我最初就没认为他是人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.04,0:07:53.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,或者他是吸血鬼也没想过
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.00,0:07:56.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他是个城堡
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.80,0:07:59.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他是移动的领土
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.76,0:08:04.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,以暴君的意志率领的死之河的民众
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.44,0:08:06.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,打到他 要怎么做才好
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.47,0:08:08.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,杀掉他要做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.13,0:08:13.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我日日夜夜都思考着这个问题
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.70,0:08:18.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因此 我只有一个战争的方法可行
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.94,0:08:21.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,战争 战争
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.72,0:08:23.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他和我的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.71,0:08:27.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,全心全力 直到无法作战
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.08,0:08:31.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我有什么 他又有什么
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.19,0:08:40.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,能使身体变化并且能操纵使役魔的力量...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.64,0:08:45.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,能使身体再生 畅饮他人的血作为粮食的吸血鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.69,0:08:51.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而这些我没有
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.71,0:08:56.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么 因为我是人类
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.00,0:08:59.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果成为吸血鬼一定很棒吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.02,0:09:01.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,无限永久的生存
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.96,0:09:04.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,无限永久持续作战
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.63,0:09:06.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那肯定是令人喜欢吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.03,0:09:10.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但我不能变成那样
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.62,0:09:13.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只有那个绝对不行
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.53,0:09:51.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不死非常好
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.81,0:09:53.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,能力炫目
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.25,0:09:58.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,以血液作为货币 交换灵魂与生命
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.42,0:10:03.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,滚开
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.79,0:10:08.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的心和灵魂以及生命都是属于我自己的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.50,0:10:11.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,与他人的命的结合
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.94,0:10:13.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,生命的融合
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.63,0:10:17.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,精神的统合 就是吸血鬼的本质
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.20,0:10:20.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,多么棒啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.66,0:10:24.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那一定是很棒的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.74,0:10:27.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那一定令人兴奋
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.34,0:10:30.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但别开玩笑了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.61,0:10:33.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我无论如何也不干
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.71,0:10:36.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的东西就是我的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.62,0:10:41.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一滴血 一根毛 都是
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.54,0:10:44.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我就是我 我就是我
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.25,0:10:47.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我就是我
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.74,0:10:50.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真叫人羡慕啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.49,0:10:55.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,耀眼而美丽 所以值得去爱 值得去恨
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.19,0:11:01.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因此 你才值得成为我的敌人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.92,0:11:06.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我终于找到了我的宿敌
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.53,0:11:09.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,属于我的战争
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.73,0:11:18.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因此 我们为之准备了很久 花了50年
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.85,0:11:29.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喵
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.86,0:11:32.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,全部都准备好了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.44,0:11:34.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,都是为了这一瞬间
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.66,0:11:38.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,最后的大队是 第九次十字军是
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.62,0:11:43.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,安德森也是 狼人部队也是 沃尔特也是
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.42,0:11:48.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所做的一切 50年来都是为了达成这一刻
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.66,0:11:54.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,当阿尔卡特 开发零氏 放出所以生命时
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.00,0:11:59.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,当他的城堡里只有他一人时
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.02,0:12:02.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,安德森能把他打倒吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.65,0:12:04.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沃尔特能把他打倒吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.84,0:12:08.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我认为是不可能的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.11,0:12:12.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就算只剩他一个 他也是可怕的吸血鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.93,0:12:16.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,100年前凭自己一人攻入伦敦的男人
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.42,0:12:22.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,500年前凭自己一人与奥斯曼帝国战斗的男人
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.54,0:12:29.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而且 只要他再吸血的话就前功尽弃了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.73,0:12:31.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这真是太狡猾了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.90,0:12:34.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对他来说 生死都是骗局
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.47,0:12:38.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如今 时刻已到
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.50,0:12:42.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样的疯狂之王怎样才能杀掉
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.81,0:12:45.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是要踏破战场上的多重阵地
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.33,0:12:50.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,然后消灭近乎无限的敌军 再取其首级吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.06,0:12:52.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不可能
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.64,0:12:55.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他一定会再吸血的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.63,0:12:58.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而且会像个大胃王一样
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.68,0:13:02.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是他最强的武器 同时也是他的弱点
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.74,0:13:08.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,古往今来 被人毒杀的暴君可不少
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.34,0:14:00.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行了 太强了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.68,0:14:19.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行了 不行
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.52,0:14:23.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂 喂 搞什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.71,0:14:27.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一点都不像你
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.70,0:14:29.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,站起来
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.29,0:14:34.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我认识的那个女孩绝不会轻易放弃的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.21,0:14:45.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真没办法 你这丫头
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.44,0:14:49.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,发什么呆 你这笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.78,0:14:53.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好了看起来总算清醒了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.25,0:14:55.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那上吧 小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.40,0:14:57.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,收拾他
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.11,0:15:00.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一起去把那家伙收拾掉
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.43,0:15:09.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不能单纯这点攻击
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.33,0:15:12.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大范围 用大范围攻击
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.55,0:15:20.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,干掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.50,0:15:21.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还没有
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.31,0:15:37.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样都没用啊 果然真是个怪物
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.88,0:15:40.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看来是如假包换的狼人了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.39,0:15:42.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,狼人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.02,0:15:48.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,金牙
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.64,0:15:49.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这种东西
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.27,0:15:52.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么 这里全都是...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.77,0:15:53.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.03,0:15:59.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这就是他们50年前在欧洲反复掠夺所得到的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.48,0:16:06.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这里的东西都是从大家 大家那里\N连这颗金牙也
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.24,0:16:11.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不知在哪个集中营里 不知从哪个可怜虫的嘴巴里拔下来的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.87,0:16:14.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,总之 他们就是一帮这样的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.50,0:16:17.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,根本不配称为军队
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.90,0:16:20.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只能说是杀人集团
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.94,0:16:24.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我是绝对不会承认这帮混蛋的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.03,0:16:27.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,无敌的军队？ 钢铁的骑士？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.59,0:16:31.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哈哈 别笑死人了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.13,0:16:37.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,银牙
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.71,0:16:41.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这到底....
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.64,0:16:43.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还真是为人着想啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.74,0:16:44.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有这个就能做到了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.95,0:16:47.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么 他居然特意...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.60,0:16:53.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 想死的可怜虫
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.13,0:16:55.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,让我们来引导他吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.40,0:16:59.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,引导也不是贝尔德特队长说了算
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.41,0:17:02.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哈哈哈 真是小气
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.58,0:17:05.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但请你不要在我里面吸烟好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.08,0:17:08.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,过来了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.22,0:17:12.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要躲开 当下来试试
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.84,0:17:13.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.52,0:17:25.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去吧 去吧 可以做到
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.84,0:17:28.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙攻击时也要实体化
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.78,0:17:31.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还没完呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.84,0:17:37.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还没完呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.69,0:17:55.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被看穿了 不用在意
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.95,0:17:56.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 我来了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.13,0:17:58.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.02,0:18:18.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这次 你是死定了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.28,0:18:25.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这位狼人小哥
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.60,0:18:30.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是50年前不知道什么人留给你的报应
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.28,0:18:33.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,收下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.28,0:18:43.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,叫你别对别人的女人下手
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.86,0:18:46.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,终于脱掉项圈了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.76,0:18:49.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,永别了 你这个军犬
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.64,0:19:18.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,简直 简直就像个做了好梦的小孩一样
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.68,0:19:23.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没错 肯定是在今晚 今夜 这个时候
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.06,0:19:27.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是他们达成一切之夜的美梦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.93,0:19:31.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,贝尔纳特队长
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.88,0:19:33.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊 就是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.90,0:19:36.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去终结掉一切吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.23,0:19:41.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没有梦是醒不过了的 去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.50,0:20:10.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,少校
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.47,0:20:21.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哟 终于能和你面对面真是高兴
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.55,0:20:32.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很遗憾 那把枪是没有用的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.81,0:20:36.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为 作为指挥者是很谨慎的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.02,0:20:47.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我本来还以为赶不及了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.65,0:20:50.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你能赶上真是太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.01,0:20:54.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这可是今晚才有的难得演出啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.82,0:20:59.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么能不请美丽的贵妇人到最好的位置观看呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.21,0:21:04.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,别开玩笑了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.12,0:21:09.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,尽情的欣赏好了 请你
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.78,0:21:18.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是百年才有一夜的戏剧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.25,0:21:26.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是自1898年以来的故事
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.97,0:21:36.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吸血鬼阿尔卡特是怎样灰飞烟灭的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.82,0:21:37.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.79,0:22:22.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,暴饮暴食也不错
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.26,0:22:32.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么 要继续吗 沃尔特
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.28,0:22:37.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还不行 我还没有 分出胜负来
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.39,0:22:39.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还没有到时间
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.04,0:22:42.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,少校 住手
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.94,0:22:45.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,给我住手 少校
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.26,0:22:49.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不 时间已经到了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.72,0:22:51.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,已经太迟了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.64,0:22:53.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,已经太迟了 一切都
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.05,0:22:58.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,已经太迟了 笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.83,0:23:09.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么都太迟了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.25,0:23:13.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你已经无法赢了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.32,0:23:18.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你已接近 但永远地失去了那个机会
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.05,0:23:22.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,难得我给了你千载难逢的机会
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.04,0:23:27.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只有两次能物理性地打倒阿尔卡特的机会
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.83,0:23:33.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,自1898年以来只出现过两次的好机
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.33,0:23:38.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,1000名吸血鬼武装亲卫队
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.86,0:23:44.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,3000人的第九次空中机动十字军
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.14,0:23:47.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,以及梵蒂冈
Dialogue: 0,0:23:48.15,0:23:50.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,以及狼人部队
Dialogue: 0,0:23:50.97,0:23:53.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,以及安德森
Dialogue: 0,0:23:54.52,0:23:58.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,以及你至今为止的半生
Dialogue: 0,0:23:58.60,0:24:02.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,牺牲了这全部才创造出的刹那
Dialogue: 0,0:24:02.97,0:24:06.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,唯一能把阿尔卡特杀掉的刹那
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.09,0:24:11.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,即使如此你的线还是没法做到
Dialogue: 0,0:24:11.35,0:24:12.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只能到此为止
Dialogue: 0,0:24:12.99,0:24:16.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而现在阿尔卡特的生命数量是多少呢
Dialogue: 0,0:24:17.24,0:24:20.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,100万吗  200万吗
Dialogue: 0,0:24:21.66,0:24:24.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对你来说已经不可能赢了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:24.49,0:24:28.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你的人生如今已经毫无价值了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:30.36,0:24:32.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要发呆啊 小鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:24:32.82,0:24:33.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,加油啊
Dialogue: 0,0:24:34.46,0:24:36.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只要再杀我大概几万次就行了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:40.45,0:24:43.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,连安德森都赢不了我
Dialogue: 0,0:24:44.22,0:24:47.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而像你这种脸色都不好的臭小鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:24:48.32,0:24:51.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就算再过50年还是500年
Dialogue: 0,0:24:51.90,0:24:53.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一样也不可能赢得了我
Dialogue: 0,0:25:00.20,0:25:03.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是你输了 阿尔卡特
Dialogue: 0,0:25:08.84,0:25:10.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我赢了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:14.35,0:25:18.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是你输了 阿尔卡特
Dialogue: 0,0:25:20.33,0:25:22.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,输？ 你说谁啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:25:23.92,0:25:25.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:25:26.82,0:25:29.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,会输  我会输吗
Dialogue: 0,0:25:30.78,0:25:33.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你说我会被你们打倒
Dialogue: 0,0:25:33.93,0:25:35.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Hellsing教授
Dialogue: 0,0:25:37.25,0:25:42.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我是不断的魔剑  没有可能会输
Dialogue: 0,0:25:42.85,0:25:43.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,绝对
Dialogue: 0,0:25:46.21,0:25:47.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:25:48.95,0:25:50.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我看到了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:25:52.18,0:25:55.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么 这场景是
Dialogue: 0,0:25:56.10,0:25:57.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个似曾相识的光景是
Dialogue: 0,0:26:05.54,0:26:07.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊 是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:26:13.21,0:26:14.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是那样
Dialogue: 0,0:26:19.85,0:26:21.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:26:32.70,0:26:36.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个时候也 有着这样的阳光
Dialogue: 0,0:26:41.84,0:26:43.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我死去时的光景
Dialogue: 0,0:26:44.78,0:26:47.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一直都是这样子的
Dialogue: 0,0:26:49.45,0:26:51.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而好几次我都这样觉得
Dialogue: 0,0:26:52.95,0:26:57.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阳光会是 如此美丽的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:27:14.36,0:27:16.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,消失吧 消失吧
Dialogue: 0,0:27:17.17,0:27:18.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,随着这短烛一起
Dialogue: 0,0:27:19.53,0:27:23.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,人生不过是个行走的影子
Dialogue: 0,0:27:35.35,0:27:38.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么 究竟发生了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:27:39.41,0:27:40.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你到底做了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:27:41.35,0:27:43.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么都没做
Dialogue: 0,0:27:45.88,0:27:49.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他把薛定鳄中尉的生命吸收了
Dialogue: 0,0:27:50.20,0:27:55.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那样除了和薛定谔的命的性质同化外还会发生什么
Dialogue: 0,0:27:57.29,0:28:03.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他是带有意志  会进行进行自我观察的薛定谔的猫
Dialogue: 0,0:28:03.97,0:28:07.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他自身不过是一只在这个变幻莫测的世界中...
Dialogue: 0,0:28:08.91,0:28:10.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,乱窜的智者之猫
Dialogue: 0,0:28:11.78,0:28:14.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在他认识到自己之前
Dialogue: 0,0:28:14.45,0:28:17.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他能存在于任何地方 也不存在于任何地方
Dialogue: 0,0:28:19.32,0:28:25.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是如今他已经融入到几百万的意识和生命中去了
Dialogue: 0,0:28:26.63,0:28:31.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,已经连他自己都不能认识到自己了
Dialogue: 0,0:28:36.89,0:28:38.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么 会怎样呢
Dialogue: 0,0:28:39.93,0:28:42.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他已经不存在于任何地方
Dialogue: 0,0:28:42.87,0:28:45.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,既不是生 也不是死
Dialogue: 0,0:28:46.71,0:28:49.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以如今的阿尔卡特
Dialogue: 0,0:28:50.94,0:28:53.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不过是虚数的集合体而已
Dialogue: 0,0:28:54.22,0:28:55.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿尔卡特
Dialogue: 0,0:28:57.74,0:28:58.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要闭上眼
Dialogue: 0,0:29:01.71,0:29:02.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把眼睛睁开
Dialogue: 0,0:29:09.11,0:29:10.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿尔卡特
Dialogue: 0,0:29:15.36,0:29:17.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是命令 阿尔卡特
Dialogue: 0,0:29:29.11,0:29:30.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不许消失
Dialogue: 0,0:29:35.71,0:29:36.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,0:29:37.67,0:29:38.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再见了
Dialogue: 0,0:29:40.22,0:29:42.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因特古拉
Dialogue: 0,0:30:22.36,0:30:24.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿尔卡特
Dialogue: 0,0:30:32.50,0:30:35.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我一切的一切都付出去了
Dialogue: 0,0:30:37.41,0:30:40.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为了将他的一切一切全部都消于无形
Dialogue: 0,0:30:46.53,0:30:48.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为着这一天而活着
Dialogue: 0,0:30:49.58,0:30:53.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为了这一瞬间而活着
Dialogue: 0,0:30:55.12,0:30:58.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我那不断失败的战争
Dialogue: 0,0:30:58.69,0:31:00.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,第一次胜利了
Dialogue: 0,0:31:02.77,0:31:05.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你 你竟然
Dialogue: 0,0:31:06.07,0:31:09.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此 确实很不错呢
Dialogue: 0,0:31:10.69,0:31:14.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这就是 胜利的滋味了
Dialogue: 0,0:31:37.42,0:31:39.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,果然是你们
Dialogue: 0,0:31:40.58,0:31:43.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要杀死我的人
Dialogue: 0,0:32:16.75,0:32:18.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,死掉了 死掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:19.11,0:32:21.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,消失了 消失了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:32.87,0:32:39.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可恶  我所希望的就是这个吗
Dialogue: 0,0:32:40.61,0:32:42.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是这样吗
Dialogue: 0,0:32:43.80,0:32:45.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是这样了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:33:01.93,0:33:05.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,死吧 死吧 死吧 给我去死吧
Dialogue: 0,0:33:05.68,0:33:07.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你竟然做出这样的事
Dialogue: 0,0:33:08.54,0:33:09.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我要杀了你
Dialogue: 0,0:33:15.40,0:33:18.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 这就是末路啊
Dialogue: 0,0:33:19.05,0:33:21.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,叛徒可悲的末路啊
Dialogue: 0,0:33:22.44,0:33:25.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不像话 我还没死去啊
Dialogue: 0,0:33:31.66,0:33:34.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么吸血鬼 什么死神
Dialogue: 0,0:33:35.74,0:33:38.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看我直接了当的把你杀了
Dialogue: 0,0:33:43.29,0:33:47.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,开   枪     吧
Dialogue: 0,0:33:51.11,0:33:52.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,继续开枪
Dialogue: 0,0:33:53.14,0:33:53.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,开枪啊
Dialogue: 0,0:33:54.81,0:33:57.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好 我就给你个痛快
Dialogue: 0,0:34:05.83,0:34:08.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还没死 还没死
Dialogue: 0,0:34:11.22,0:34:14.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我要开枪 继续开枪 不断地开枪
Dialogue: 0,0:34:20.54,0:34:23.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你要对我开枪就随你好了
Dialogue: 0,0:34:24.96,0:34:25.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不过
Dialogue: 0,0:34:27.76,0:34:30.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可以杀死我的并不是你
Dialogue: 0,0:34:37.88,0:34:39.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等一下 等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:34:40.39,0:34:42.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等一下 给我等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:34:43.40,0:34:51.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我要杀了你 杀了你 杀了你....
Dialogue: 0,0:35:21.46,0:35:24.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哟 出次见面 小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:35:27.62,0:35:30.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如今事情已经很明确了
Dialogue: 0,0:35:31.36,0:35:33.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没错  就是你们
Dialogue: 0,0:35:35.95,0:35:39.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,并不是阿尔卡特打倒了我
Dialogue: 0,0:35:39.69,0:35:42.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而是我打倒了阿尔卡特
Dialogue: 0,0:35:49.40,0:35:52.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的宿敌是阿尔卡特
Dialogue: 0,0:35:52.75,0:35:56.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们的宿敌如今是我了
Dialogue: 0,0:35:59.92,0:36:07.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,来吧 敌人在这里 就在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:36:09.08,0:36:14.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们就在那里  我就在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:36:16.70,0:36:18.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:36:23.19,0:36:23.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,塞拉斯
Dialogue: 0,0:36:25.62,0:36:26.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,攻击
Dialogue: 0,0:36:27.40,0:36:28.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,攻击 攻击
Dialogue: 0,0:36:30.82,0:36:36.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,见敌必杀 见敌必杀
Dialogue: 0,0:36:47.55,0:36:50.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,臭博士 做得硬过头了
Dialogue: 0,0:37:09.60,0:37:12.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Acht-Acht88 这东西太棒了
Dialogue: 0,0:37:13.10,0:37:13.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我最喜欢了
Dialogue: 0,0:37:54.42,0:37:56.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你完蛋了 少校
Dialogue: 0,0:37:59.09,0:38:03.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好像 确实如此
Dialogue: 0,0:38:04.54,0:38:07.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,才怪 还早呢
Dialogue: 0,0:38:09.05,0:38:10.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是
Dialogue: 0,0:38:10.38,0:38:12.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这就是你的真面目吗 少校
Dialogue: 0,0:38:15.52,0:38:19.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没错 这就是我了
Dialogue: 0,0:38:21.22,0:38:22.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,机械
Dialogue: 0,0:38:25.67,0:38:33.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你这话说得太失礼了 小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:38:34.80,0:38:37.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我可是个真正的人类
Dialogue: 0,0:38:40.70,0:38:42.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怪物
Dialogue: 0,0:38:43.50,0:38:45.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你只是个怪物
Dialogue: 0,0:38:46.53,0:38:50.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不对 我是人类
Dialogue: 0,0:38:52.34,0:38:56.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,区分是否为人类的方法只有一种
Dialogue: 0,0:38:57.79,0:38:59.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是自我的意志
Dialogue: 0,0:39:01.24,0:39:03.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要把我和那种将血液作为灵魂的货币...
Dialogue: 0,0:39:05.49,0:39:09.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不持续吸收他人就无法生存下去
Dialogue: 0,0:39:10.77,0:39:14.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿尔卡特那样的可怜怪物...
Dialogue: 0,0:39:15.44,0:39:18.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那样弱小的家伙混为一谈
Dialogue: 0,0:39:20.14,0:39:23.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只要我的意志依然存在
Dialogue: 0,0:39:24.23,0:39:33.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哪怕我只剩下漂浮在玻璃瓶里的营养液之中的脑髓也好
Dialogue: 0,0:39:34.79,0:39:41.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就算我已经变成了巨大计算机里的记忆回路也好
Dialogue: 0,0:39:42.95,0:39:45.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我依然是人类
Dialogue: 0,0:39:46.26,0:39:52.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,人类就是灵魂的心的意志的生物
Dialogue: 0,0:39:55.21,0:40:00.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就算他以年幼的少女的形态露出微笑也好
Dialogue: 0,0:40:01.39,0:40:07.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,以久经沙场的战士的形象发出许多的感伤也好
Dialogue: 0,0:40:07.63,0:40:09.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他依然是怪物
Dialogue: 0,0:40:10.99,0:40:16.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因此 我从心底里憎恨着他
Dialogue: 0,0:40:17.84,0:40:21.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,绝对不承认吸血鬼阿尔卡特
Dialogue: 0,0:40:23.21,0:40:26.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他是有着人类外表的怪物的话
Dialogue: 0,0:40:27.08,0:40:30.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那我就是有着怪物外表的人类了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:40:31.57,0:40:33.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我就是我
Dialogue: 0,0:40:40.60,0:40:42.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这归这
Dialogue: 0,0:40:43.60,0:40:46.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我和你们是不同的
Dialogue: 0,0:40:47.16,0:40:51.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个世上的所有斗争对我来说就是一切
Dialogue: 0,0:40:52.33,0:40:55.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,人类就是为此而生于这个世上
Dialogue: 0,0:40:56.21,0:41:01.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但你也不会认同我说的话吧
Dialogue: 0,0:41:02.46,0:41:06.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,老早以前的宣战布告就已经这么说过了
Dialogue: 0,0:41:07.58,0:41:12.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,来吧 进行战争吧
Dialogue: 0,0:42:30.53,0:42:32.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,第一次打中了
Dialogue: 0,0:43:00.08,0:43:02.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这真是美好
Dialogue: 0,0:43:06.66,0:43:08.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美好的战争啊
Dialogue: 0,0:43:09.40,0:43:11.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美好的战争啊
Dialogue: 0,0:43:19.59,0:43:23.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,死吧 你就应该这样去死
Dialogue: 0,0:43:28.74,0:43:32.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美好的战争吗 少校
Dialogue: 0,0:43:42.28,0:43:44.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这根本不能成为战争
Dialogue: 0,0:43:45.52,0:43:50.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在死亡边缘挣扎了60年 你已仅仅剩下最后一口气
Dialogue: 0,0:43:51.53,0:43:53.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你必须得死
Dialogue: 0,0:43:54.34,0:43:55.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这绝对是报应
Dialogue: 0,0:43:57.90,0:44:00.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你再怎么保持你是人类的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:44:00.93,0:44:03.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你的外壳已不是人类
Dialogue: 0,0:44:05.11,0:44:08.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你只是个真正的怪物
Dialogue: 0,0:44:12.64,0:44:15.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,打倒怪物的总是人类
Dialogue: 0,0:44:17.23,0:44:19.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怪物将人类打倒的话
Dialogue: 0,0:44:20.44,0:44:23.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,人类会以打倒你为目的
Dialogue: 0,0:44:24.57,0:44:26.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,战斗永不会停止
Dialogue: 0,0:44:27.44,0:44:29.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你的纳粹主义就是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:44:33.65,0:44:36.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你不是人类
Dialogue: 0,0:44:37.83,0:44:40.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以他一定会回来
Dialogue: 0,0:44:51.20,0:44:52.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就这样结束了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:44:55.04,0:44:56.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不 不可能
Dialogue: 0,0:44:56.41,0:44:57.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不应该这样
Dialogue: 0,0:44:58.26,0:45:00.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,技术是推动理学发展的动力
Dialogue: 0,0:45:00.71,0:45:01.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,研究帮助我们进化超越
Dialogue: 0,0:45:02.29,0:45:04.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不 不 研究已经使得我们进化超越了
Dialogue: 0,0:45:06.28,0:45:07.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我该怎么办才好
Dialogue: 0,0:45:07.66,0:45:08.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我该怎么办才好
Dialogue: 0,0:45:09.52,0:45:11.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么 什么
Dialogue: 0,0:45:16.52,0:45:18.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还没有 还没有结束
Dialogue: 0,0:45:19.71,0:45:21.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么留下了  什么要带走
Dialogue: 0,0:45:22.49,0:45:24.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊！是啊！ 某一天！未来的某一天！
Dialogue: 0,0:45:24.95,0:45:25.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,遍布整个世界
Dialogue: 0,0:45:27.48,0:45:29.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,散布到全世界
Dialogue: 0,0:45:30.49,0:45:32.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,科学的背后是奇迹
Dialogue: 0,0:45:33.04,0:45:34.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,奇迹的背后也是科学
Dialogue: 0,0:45:35.19,0:45:38.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,到哪里都没有 古兰博士
Dialogue: 0,0:45:39.19,0:45:40.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行不行博士
Dialogue: 0,0:45:41.08,0:45:43.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太执着也是不好的
Dialogue: 0,0:45:43.65,0:45:45.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沃尔特
Dialogue: 0,0:45:47.60,0:45:50.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,作为纳粹最后残党的最后一人
Dialogue: 0,0:45:50.71,0:45:52.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这根本连个笑话都不算
Dialogue: 0,0:45:53.13,0:45:53.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你
Dialogue: 0,0:45:54.19,0:45:55.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你这毫无意义的丧家之犬
Dialogue: 0,0:45:56.35,0:45:59.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你自己也是条毫无意义的丧家之犬啊 博士
Dialogue: 0,0:46:00.12,0:46:03.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你  以及你创造的一切
Dialogue: 0,0:46:04.07,0:46:05.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也包括我自己
Dialogue: 0,0:46:05.98,0:46:07.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,闹剧要结束了
Dialogue: 0,0:46:07.98,0:46:09.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,演员也该退场了
Dialogue: 0,0:46:10.37,0:46:13.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我说的对吧 大博士
Dialogue: 0,0:46:13.62,0:46:15.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,闹剧 你说是闹剧
Dialogue: 0,0:46:16.39,0:46:17.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你凭什么这么说
Dialogue: 0,0:46:18.27,0:46:20.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就凭你这不良品吗
Dialogue: 0,0:46:20.73,0:46:23.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这一夜 这一幕都是闹剧
Dialogue: 0,0:46:24.10,0:46:26.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这场斗争也是 这个世界也是
Dialogue: 0,0:46:28.13,0:46:28.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也
Dialogue: 0,0:46:29.46,0:46:33.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也只是在其中扮演着自己该做到的角色而已
Dialogue: 0,0:46:46.30,0:46:47.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是凄惨的末路啊
Dialogue: 0,0:46:48.27,0:46:50.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿尔卡特说得对
Dialogue: 0,0:46:50.48,0:46:52.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,叫人看不下去啊
Dialogue: 0,0:46:52.64,0:46:54.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,像你这样的不良品
Dialogue: 0,0:46:55.47,0:46:56.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,像你这样的失败品
Dialogue: 0,0:46:57.36,0:46:59.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,竟敢嘲笑我们吗
Dialogue: 0,0:47:00.10,0:47:04.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,像你这样的人可以嘲笑我的研究只是闹剧吗
Dialogue: 0,0:47:04.65,0:47:07.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可以嘲笑少校大人的大队吗
Dialogue: 0,0:47:08.24,0:47:09.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就凭你这样子
Dialogue: 0,0:47:09.85,0:47:11.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就凭你这样的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:47:12.35,0:47:14.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,理论正在飞跃 研究正在飞跃
Dialogue: 0,0:47:15.66,0:47:18.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,自然科学会通过实践而不断前进
Dialogue: 0,0:47:18.94,0:47:20.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,总有一天会追上这个
Dialogue: 0,0:47:21.16,0:47:22.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,总有一天把阿尔卡特超越给你看
Dialogue: 0,0:47:23.74,0:47:25.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,别再说傻话了
Dialogue: 0,0:47:25.59,0:47:27.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你和我都要死了
Dialogue: 0,0:47:28.26,0:47:29.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不良品全都要死
Dialogue: 0,0:47:30.10,0:47:31.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,给我闭嘴
Dialogue: 0,0:47:43.07,0:47:44.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,米娜哈克
Dialogue: 0,0:47:45.74,0:47:46.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我就知道是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:47:47.32,0:47:49.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这就是你们的教材
Dialogue: 0,0:47:50.64,0:47:55.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿尔卡特还是德库拉时唯一进行过初拥的存在
Dialogue: 0,0:47:56.29,0:47:57.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一切的开始
Dialogue: 0,0:47:59.14,0:48:02.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,据说在海辛教授打倒德库拉拉之后就变回了人类
Dialogue: 0,0:48:03.83,0:48:06.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是阿尔卡特并没有死去
Dialogue: 0,0:48:07.04,0:48:10.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿尔卡特依然存在于她之中
Dialogue: 0,0:48:12.77,0:48:17.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不论她自身怎么样  都在她体内极深处存在着
Dialogue: 0,0:48:18.45,0:48:23.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,无论圣饼还是圣水还是十字架都无法生效的吸血鬼之血
Dialogue: 0,0:48:24.72,0:48:27.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以你们从这里开始了
Dialogue: 0,0:48:29.17,0:48:31.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,模仿阿尔卡特
Dialogue: 0,0:48:32.28,0:48:35.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为此你们把她挖了出来
Dialogue: 0,0:48:35.69,0:48:39.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,摧残已经变成残骸的她
Dialogue: 0,0:48:47.29,0:48:51.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,到头来你们所做的是不过是盗版而已
Dialogue: 0,0:48:52.42,0:48:55.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样还不是闹剧又是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:48:59.81,0:49:01.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是可怜啊 米娜
Dialogue: 0,0:49:02.18,0:49:03.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,全部都消失吧
Dialogue: 0,0:49:03.67,0:49:04.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是时候退场了
Dialogue: 0,0:49:05.65,0:49:07.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们也是我也是
Dialogue: 0,0:49:15.16,0:49:16.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,正中目标
Dialogue: 0,0:49:27.59,0:49:29.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊啊 可恶
Dialogue: 0,0:49:31.34,0:49:34.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真想赢过那个家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:49:40.74,0:49:41.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,永别了
Dialogue: 0,0:49:43.23,0:49:44.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:49:54.47,0:49:55.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沃尔特
Dialogue: 0,0:50:02.72,0:50:04.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沃尔特死去了
Dialogue: 0,0:50:05.10,0:50:06.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就在刚才
Dialogue: 0,0:50:09.49,0:50:10.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:50:17.33,0:50:18.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:50:19.36,0:50:20.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,回去吧  塞拉斯
Dialogue: 0,0:50:22.57,0:50:23.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,回我们的家
Dialogue: 0,0:50:25.95,0:50:26.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,飞吧
Dialogue: 0,0:52:10.27,0:52:14.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,英美被袭击事件 别名特殊战事件
Dialogue: 0,0:52:14.52,0:52:15.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,第911次报告
Dialogue: 0,0:52:16.69,0:52:21.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,遇难者 美国673918名
Dialogue: 0,0:52:22.25,0:52:26.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,英国3918931名
Dialogue: 0,0:52:29.19,0:52:33.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今天统计这些损失吗 这样做好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:52:34.92,0:52:38.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好 不久我就回去
Dialogue: 0,0:52:40.62,0:52:43.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再一次回想30年前的事件
Dialogue: 0,0:52:44.37,0:52:47.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,统计武器损失也是我的责任
Dialogue: 0,0:52:50.20,0:52:54.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,爱尔兰 你总是这幅嘴脸
Dialogue: 0,0:52:54.74,0:52:57.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,和你爷爷真像
Dialogue: 0,0:53:09.57,0:53:11.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,到此为止 胜负已分
Dialogue: 0,0:53:12.25,0:53:13.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因特古拉大人赢了
Dialogue: 0,0:53:15.76,0:53:17.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,（2030年 伦敦）
Dialogue: 0,0:53:20.67,0:53:22.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,漂亮 漂亮
Dialogue: 0,0:53:22.54,0:53:25.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,身手真是一点也没变迟钝
Dialogue: 0,0:53:25.66,0:53:26.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,十三科的
Dialogue: 0,0:53:27.37,0:53:29.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我应该有要你们在招待室等待的
Dialogue: 0,0:53:30.35,0:53:34.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不不不 只是光等待不符合我们的性格
Dialogue: 0,0:53:35.08,0:53:38.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而且在等的时候连一杯茶都没有
Dialogue: 0,0:53:39.22,0:53:41.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,稍微有点无聊就过来了
Dialogue: 0,0:53:41.83,0:53:43.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,让你们随便乱走会让我很难做的
Dialogue: 0,0:53:44.70,0:53:45.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,麻烦给我回去
Dialogue: 0,0:53:46.90,0:53:49.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好的 好的 那就回去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:54:03.32,0:54:04.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,间久部机关长
Dialogue: 0,0:54:04.70,0:54:06.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,府内的装备还是破绽百出啊
Dialogue: 0,0:54:07.63,0:54:08.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如今就能打败他们
Dialogue: 0,0:54:09.32,0:54:12.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小鬼 你的眼睛是瞎的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:54:21.26,0:54:21.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是
Dialogue: 0,0:54:22.71,0:54:24.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,塞拉斯·维克多利亚的影子
Dialogue: 0,0:54:25.85,0:54:29.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们全部都在监视之下吗
Dialogue: 0,0:54:30.36,0:54:35.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是多亏间久部机关长 圆桌会议的半数都退下台了
Dialogue: 0,0:54:36.36,0:54:38.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还不行 还未
Dialogue: 0,0:54:39.77,0:54:41.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们失去的太多了
Dialogue: 0,0:54:42.44,0:54:46.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,第九次十字军后梵蒂冈失去了太多力量了
Dialogue: 0,0:54:47.46,0:54:49.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没什么 那就等吧
Dialogue: 0,0:54:50.24,0:54:51.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们都等过500年之久了
Dialogue: 0,0:54:52.59,0:54:56.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再过100年 200年又算什么
Dialogue: 0,0:54:56.85,0:54:59.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,下回的第十次的一定可以成功
Dialogue: 0,0:55:03.95,0:55:05.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今天就到此为止
Dialogue: 0,0:55:05.76,0:55:06.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就此解散吧
Dialogue: 0,0:55:07.96,0:55:10.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,番伍德卿 辛苦你了
Dialogue: 0,0:55:11.01,0:55:11.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:55:12.16,0:55:14.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不错的剑术 你有进步了
Dialogue: 0,0:55:15.80,0:55:17.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是 啊不 还差得远
Dialogue: 0,0:55:18.10,0:55:19.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,非常感谢你的夸奖
Dialogue: 0,0:55:20.04,0:55:22.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那 那个 我的爷爷
Dialogue: 0,0:55:22.39,0:55:26.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊不 我的祖父也是学过剑术的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:55:29.30,0:55:31.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你的爷爷是
Dialogue: 0,0:55:33.25,0:55:36.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把逼近的纳粹士兵一个个的撕开
Dialogue: 0,0:55:36.38,0:55:37.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个英姿被人誉为英国无双
Dialogue: 0,0:55:38.70,0:55:40.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所有接近他的人都会变成碎片
Dialogue: 0,0:55:41.11,0:55:46.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,据说全身绑满炸药把敌人的空中战舰整个炸飞了
Dialogue: 0,0:55:49.35,0:55:50.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,英国的无双战士
Dialogue: 0,0:55:51.27,0:55:54.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这只左眼也是当时的必杀技弄的
Dialogue: 0,0:55:54.46,0:55:55.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是骗人的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:55:55.61,0:55:56.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是真的
Dialogue: 0,0:55:57.48,0:55:58.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的是真的
Dialogue: 0,0:55:59.90,0:56:01.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是真的
Dialogue: 0,0:56:02.13,0:56:05.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以新的直升机的货款就拜托你了
Dialogue: 0,0:56:05.50,0:56:06.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,又是这个啊
Dialogue: 0,0:56:07.03,0:56:08.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拜托你了
Dialogue: 0,0:56:11.22,0:56:12.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:56:18.52,0:56:21.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拜托你  真过分
Dialogue: 0,0:56:21.74,0:56:27.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是辛苦啊 那个人以及这一族的人几乎都是黑社会的谈话方式吗
Dialogue: 0,0:56:28.12,0:56:30.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样就好  能艰苦工作
Dialogue: 0,0:56:31.36,0:56:33.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,从现在开始严厉地让他艰苦工作
Dialogue: 0,0:56:35.97,0:56:38.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在我死后 Hellsing也将完结
Dialogue: 0,0:56:38.98,0:56:41.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而那个人也要独立了
Dialogue: 0,0:56:42.26,0:56:45.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,以后该由政府主导的国家机关来挑起重担
Dialogue: 0,0:56:45.97,0:56:50.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而不是由一家来统帅机关的时代了
Dialogue: 0,0:56:53.84,0:56:55.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而且我也稍微有点累了
Dialogue: 0,0:56:56.87,0:56:58.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个样子还真没见过呢
Dialogue: 0,0:56:59.33,0:57:01.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今早照镜子发现小皱纹有增多了
Dialogue: 0,0:57:04.58,0:57:05.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而看到了皱纹
Dialogue: 0,0:57:07.12,0:57:08.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就会想起沃尔特
Dialogue: 0,0:57:09.99,0:57:11.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,战斗吧 大小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:57:12.17,0:57:14.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:57:14.97,0:57:16.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要丧气 不要为此丧气
Dialogue: 0,0:57:17.24,0:57:19.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还是不行吗 还没克服吗
Dialogue: 0,0:57:19.80,0:57:21.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,请不要说什么死的
Dialogue: 0,0:57:21.86,0:57:23.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,万一有什么的话 就让我吸你的血吧
Dialogue: 0,0:57:25.72,0:57:27.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你看 你看 我在模仿主人
Dialogue: 0,0:57:28.62,0:57:29.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这可不是该踢人的场合吧
Dialogue: 0,0:57:30.73,0:57:32.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,玩笑也不许说 笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:57:32.59,0:57:34.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你都过了几十年了 还没改吗
Dialogue: 0,0:57:34.76,0:57:36.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,到底阿尔卡特那个笨蛋在干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:57:37.13,0:57:38.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么还不回来
Dialogue: 0,0:57:39.04,0:57:41.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你不是说他会回来吗
Dialogue: 0,0:57:44.99,0:57:46.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,会回来的
Dialogue: 0,0:57:47.00,0:57:48.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我很清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:57:49.40,0:57:51.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为我是被他吸过血的
Dialogue: 0,0:57:52.50,0:57:56.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说着说着就过了30年  30年了
Dialogue: 0,0:58:24.97,0:58:27.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为你是吸血鬼所以没有关系
Dialogue: 0,0:58:28.01,0:58:29.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小皱纹也不会增加呢
Dialogue: 0,0:58:30.75,0:58:31.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你这个坏孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:58:32.82,0:58:34.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是这张嘴吗 是这张嘴说的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:58:35.07,0:58:37.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 很对不起
Dialogue: 0,1:00:07.78,1:00:09.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有什么事吗  主人
Dialogue: 0,1:00:24.54,1:00:25.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是粗暴的欢迎啊
Dialogue: 0,1:00:26.75,1:00:29.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而且还是老样子 吵得要死
Dialogue: 0,1:00:30.47,1:00:31.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,主人
Dialogue: 0,1:00:33.47,1:00:35.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,归队太晚了 阿尔卡特
Dialogue: 0,1:00:37.01,1:00:38.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,到底在做什么
Dialogue: 0,1:00:40.20,1:00:41.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在不断地杀戮
Dialogue: 0,1:00:43.07,1:00:46.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在我的里面把我的生命
Dialogue: 0,1:00:49.61,1:00:53.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,三百四十二万四千八百六十七
Dialogue: 0,1:00:54.83,1:01:00.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,除了一个外 全部杀得一干二净
Dialogue: 0,1:01:03.31,1:01:05.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我现在回到了这里
Dialogue: 0,1:01:06.72,1:01:11.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我已经是存在于任何地方 也不存在于任何地方
Dialogue: 0,1:01:12.12,1:01:14.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以我在这里了
Dialogue: 0,1:01:17.60,1:01:20.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太慢了 实在太慢了
Dialogue: 0,1:01:21.63,1:01:22.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太慢了阿尔卡特
Dialogue: 0,1:01:26.04,1:01:27.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉
Dialogue: 0,1:01:29.49,1:01:32.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想吸血吗 我的
Dialogue: 0,1:01:33.93,1:01:36.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊 说的对啊
Dialogue: 0,1:01:37.22,1:01:41.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,30年来什么都没吃  肚子饿了
Dialogue: 0,1:01:52.93,1:01:55.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我已经是老太婆了
Dialogue: 0,1:01:56.68,1:01:57.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我已近
Dialogue: 0,1:02:00.62,1:02:01.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样也没关系
Dialogue: 0,1:02:26.05,1:02:29.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎回来 伯爵
Dialogue: 0,1:02:31.10,1:02:34.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了 伯爵
